Narrator: Legends.
Stories scattered through time.
Mankind has grown quite fond
of recounting the exploits
of heroes and villains,
forgetting so easily
that we are remnants, byproducts, of a forgotten past.
Man, born from dust, was strong,
wise, and resourceful.
But he was born into an unforgiving world.
An inevitable darkness, creatures of destruction.
The creatures of Grimm set
their sights on man
and all of his creations.
These forces clashed and it seemed the darkness was intent
on returning man's brief existence to the void.
However, even the
smallest spark of hope
is enough to ignite change
and in time, man's passion,
resourcefulness and ingenuity led them to the tools
that would help even the odds.
This power was appropriately named, "Dust".
Nature's wrath in hand, man lit their way through the darkness
and in the shadow's absence, came strength, civilization
and most importantly,
life.
But even the most brilliant lights
eventually flicker and die.
And when they are gone...
...darkness will return.
So, you may prepare
your guardians...
build your monuments to a
so-called free world
but take heed...
there will be no
victory in strength.
Ozpin: But perhaps victory is in
the simpler things that
you've long forgotten.
Things that require a
smaller, more honest soul.
Roman: Do you have any idea
how hard it is to find
a Dust shop open this late?
Shop owner:  P-please!
Just take my Lien and leave!
Roman: Shhh, calm down, we're not
here for your money.
Grab the dust.
Henchman: Crystals.
Burn. Uncut.
Henchman: Alright kid, put your
hands where I can see 'em.
Hey, I said hands in the air!
You got a death
wish or something!?
Ruby: Huh?
Yes?
Henchman: I said, put your
hands in the air, now!
Ruby: Are you...
robbing me?
Henchman: Yes!
Ruby: Oh.
Henchman: Hey!
Ruby: Hyah!
Henchman: Freeze!
♪ This will be the day
we're waiting for. ♪
we open up the door. ♪
♪ I don't wanna hear
your absolution. ♪
♪ Hope you're ready
for a revolution. ♪
♪ Welcome to a world
of new solutions ♪
♪ Welcome to a world of bloody evolution- ♪
Roman: Okayyy...
Get her!
- You were worth every cent.
Truly, you were.
Well, Red, I think we can all say
it's been an eventful evening,
and as much as I'd
love to stick around...
I'm afraid this is
where we part ways.
Ruby: You okay if I go after him?
Shop owner: Uh huh.
Ruby: Hey!
Roman: Persistent...
End of the line, Red.
Whoa-ho-ho!
Huh?
- We got a Huntress!
The hell...?
Ruby: You're a Huntress!
Can I have your autograph?
Glynda: I hope you realize that
your actions tonight
will not be taken lightly,
young lady.
You put yourself and
others in great danger.
Ruby: They started it!
Glynda: If it were up to me,
you'd be sent home...
With a pat on the back...
And a slap on the wrist.
Ruby: Eeek!
Glynda: But... there is someone here
who would like to meet you.
Ozpin: Ruby Rose...
You...
have silver eyes.
Ruby: Um...
Ozpin: So!
Where did you learn to do this?
Ruby: S-Signal Academy.
Ozpin: They taught you to use one
of the most dangerous
weapons ever designed?
Ruby: Well, one teacher
in particular.
Ozpin: I see...
It's just that I've only seen
one other scythe-wielder
of that skill before.
A dusty, old crow.
Ruby: Mmmm!
Thash muh unkul!
Sorry, that's my Uncle Qrow!
He's a teacher at Signal!
I was complete garbage before
he took me under his wing.
And now I'm all
like-- Hooowaaah!
Witchaaaa!
ozpin: So I've noticed.
And what is an adorable girl
such as yourself
doing at a school designed
to train warriors?
Ruby: Well...
I want to be a Huntress.
Ozpin: You want to slay monsters?
Ruby: Yeah!
I only have two more years
of training left at Signal!
And then I'm going
to apply to Beacon!
You see, my sister's
starting there this year,
and she's trying to become
a Huntress,
and I'm trying to become a Huntress 'cause I wanna help people.
My parents always taught us to
help others, so I thought,
'Hey, I might as well make
a career out of it!'
I mean the police are alright,
but Huntsman and Huntresses
are just so much more
romantic and exciting
and really, gosh, you know!
Ozpin: Do you know who I am?
Ruby: You're Professor Ozpin.
You're the headmaster of Beacon.
Ozpin: Hello.
Ruby: Nice to meet you.
Ozpin: You want to come to my school?
Ruby: More than anything.
Glynda: Hmmph.
Ozpin: Well okay.
Yang: Oh, I can't believe my
baby sister is going
to Beacon with me!
This is the best day ever!
Ruby: Please stop.
Yang: But I'm so proud of you!
Ruby: Really, Sis, it was nothing.
Yang: What do you mean?
It was incredible!
Everyone at Beacon is going to
think you're the bee's knees.
Ruby: I don't want to be
the "bee's knees", okay?
I don't wanna be
any kind of knees!
I just want to be a normal
girl with normal knees.
Yang: What's with you?
Aren't you excited?
Ruby: Of course I'm excited...
I just...
I got moved ahead two years.
I don't want people to think
I'm special or anything.
Yang: But you are special.
News reporter: ...The robbery was led by
nefarious criminal
Roman Torchwick, who continues
to evade authorities.
If you have any information
on his whereabouts
please contact the
Vale Police Department.
Back to you, Lisa.
Lisa: Thank you, Cyril.
In other news, this Saturday's
Faunus Civil Right's protest
turned dark when
members of the White Fang
disrupted the ceremony.
The once peaceful
organization has now disrupted...
Glynda: Hello, and welcome to Beacon!
Yang: Who's that?
Glynda: My name is Glynda Goodwitch.
Yang: Oh.
Glynda: You are among a privileged few
who have received the honor of
being selected to attend
this prestigious academy!
Our world is experiencing an
incredible time of peace,
and as future Huntsman
and Huntresses,
it is your duty to uphold it.
You have demonstrated the
courage needed for such a task,
and now, it is our turn to provide
you with the knowledge
and the training to
protect our world.
Ruby: Wow!
Look, you can see
Signal from up here!
- I guess home isn't
too far after all!
Yang: Beacon's our home, now.
- Well... I guess the view
isn't for everyone.
Ruby: It was a nice moment
while it lasted.
I wonder who we're gonna meet.
Ruby: I just hope they're better
than "Vomit Boy".
- Oh, Yang, gross, you have puke
on your shoe!
Yang: Gross, gross, gross...
Ruby: Get away get away!
Get away from me!
♪ They see you as small
and helpless ♪
♪ They see you as just a child ♪
♪ Surprise when they
find out that a warrior
will soon run wild ♪
♪ Prepare for your
greatest moments ♪
♪ Prepare for your finest hour ♪
♪ The dream that you've
always dreamed
is suddenly about to flower. ♪
♪ We are lightning straying
from the thunder ♪
♪ Miracle of ancient wonder ♪
♪ This will be the day
we're waiting for. ♪
we open up the door. ♪
♪ I don't wanna hear
your absolution. ♪
♪ Hope you're ready
for a revolution. ♪
♪ Welcome to a world
of new solutions ♪
♪ Welcome to a world of
bloody evolution ♪
♪ In time your heart
will open minds ♪
♪ A story will be told ♪
♪ And victory is in
a simple soul. ♪♪♪